[
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『👁️🔥☠️』",
      "response": "ايتاشي"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『😴⚡』",
      "response": "زينتسو"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『👶🧠👓』",
      "response": "كونان"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『☘️💪📕』",
      "response": "استا"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『⚔️🗡️🗺️』",
      "response": "زورو"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🌪️📗🧞‍♀️』",
      "response": "يونو"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🌬️🔥🗡️』",
      "response": "تانجيرو"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🥷🍜🦊』",
      "response": "ناروتو"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🍩🌬️🔥』",
      "response": "رينغوكو"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『📓🖋️☠️』",
      "response": "كيرا"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🏀👊🍩』",
      "response": "اكازا"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『👨‍🦲👊』",
      "response": "سايتاما"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🚀🌍👶🦍』",
      "response": "غوكو"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『👦🎣』",
      "response": "غون"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『👒』",
      "response": "لوفي"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『😴👪⚒️』",
      "response": "اياناكوجي"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🥅⚽👦🏻』",
      "response": "عامر"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『⚽⛹🏻👟』",
      "response": "ايساغي"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🌬️🌫️』",
      "response": "توكيتو"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🌬️🪨』",
      "response": "جيومي"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🗡️🌬️☀️』",
      "response": "يوريتشي"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🌬️🫦💞』",
      "response": "ميتسوري"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🦋🌬️』",
      "response": "شينوبو"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي 『👁️👁️👁️👁️👁️👁️🌕🌬️』",
      "response": "كوكوشيبو"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『❄️👹』",
      "response": "دوما"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🥷⚡👁️📗』",
      "response": "كاكاشي"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🪡🍽️💪』",
      "response": "ميدوريا"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『☝️🍽️💪』",
      "response": "سوكونا"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🌍☠️🕊️』",
      "response": "ايرين"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『👒🍩』",
      "response": "ايس"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🧠🍰』",
      "response": "ال"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🐐💪』",
      "response": "تشوبر"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🪄🍲📙』",
      "response": "تشارمي"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『👧🔥👹』",
      "response": "نيزوكو"
  },
  {
      "question": " احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『👧🥜🧠💭』",
      "response": "انيا"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🥯💪🏋🏻』",
      "response": "ماش"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『👨‍🦰🗡️😇』",
      "response": "ايتشيغو"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🦇🥷』",
      "response": "باتمان"
  },
  {
      "question": "احزر الشخصيه من الايموجي『🎭🌃👩‍👩‍👧』",
      "response": "شادو"

}
]
